

About

Address: Ataşehir / İstanbul

Phone: +905076935005

Birthdate: 16/06/1994

Email: orkungedik90@gmail.com

Github: www.github.com/orkungdk

Languages

English - Advanced Turkish - Native

Certifications

- ➤ Atlassian Certificated Jira Administrator (ACP-100)
- ➤ Certification of enriching your applications with Nuxt.js
- ➤ Certification of master docker with Java – Devops for Spring Microservices

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science (2013 - 2018)

Ozyegin University (%75 scholarship)

Orkun Gedik

Summary

Full-stack developer specializing in both front end and backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycles. Well-versed in numerous programming languages especially Java, Python and Vue.js. By working in different projects in different companies, I have a strong background in terms of adaptation and technology diversity.

Professional Skill Highlights

Programming Languages

- > JAVA
- ➤ Pyhton
- ➤ Vue.js
- ➤ SQL (MySQL / Oracle)
- ➤ Groovy
- > PowerShell / Bash

Frameworks & Tools

- > Microservices
- ➤ Spring Boot
- ➤ Hibernate
- ≻Git
- ➤ Maven / Gradle
- ➤ Docker
- ➤ Kubernetes
- ➤ Bamboo / Jenkins
- > Apache Kafka

Experience

Amadeus (September 2019 – Currently)

Software Developer - Loyalty

As a part of the functional development team in the Loyalty Community Project my responsibilities are as follows:

- Back-end development, testing, and automation using various languages (Java/Python) and frameworks (Spring Boot/JPA)
- Maintenance of backward compatibility, configurability, and code quality which are quite important since Loyalty is a big scale on-going community project.
- Solution proposals, technical analysis, technical point of contact for one of the most important modules in Loyalty (Tier).
- ➤ Leading an open source project and mentoring interns who works for that project.

Softtech (May 2019 – September 2019)

Full stack Developer - Rally

As a part of Rally architecture team, my responsibilities were:

- Maintaining the rally framework and add new functinalities according to business teams' needs.
- Improvement of the current technologies, structure and application design.

OBSS (February 2018 – May 2019)

Solution Architect / Software Developer - Atlassian

- Focused on Atlassian tool solution design, architecture, and implementation.
- Finding suitable solutions for customers.
- Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment.
- Integrating applications and tools in different environments and technology stacks
- > DevOps transformations.
- > Plugin development for Atlassian tools.